Guide to the Washington State University Theatre and Dance Records 1924-2011
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 3: Scrapbooks, 1943-1972.
  - Clippings, correspondence, programs, photographs (green cover album). Broken into five sections: Commedians, 1970-1971; Commedians, 1971-1972; Music tours, 1970-1971; Brass symposium, 1971; Women's conference, 1972. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, programs, and clippings. 1950-1959. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, programs, and clippings. 1960-1968. Includes some writings and photographs of Raymond Jones at back, 1943-1969. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, programs, and photographs. 1962-1967. (Box 13, Folder 1)